A Guide to the Records of the Secretary of the Commonwealth, 1996-2006
Library of Virginia
- Series IX. Restoration of Rights Files, 1996-2006 (accessions 42418 and 42513) RESTRICTED FOR 75 YEARS., Extent: 47.60 cu. ft. (Box 138-274)
  - Subseries B: Governor Mark R. Warner, 2002-2006.
    - 15 January 2004 to 14 January 2005 (Accession 42418)
      - Nickolas, Anthony Mark, granted 15 March 2004 (Box 207, Folder 19)
      - Nikzai, Nadir A., granted 26 July 2004 (Box 207, Folder 20)
      - Nobles, Richard James, granted 30 December 2004 (Box 207, Folder 21)
      - Nolan, Michael Edward, granted 28 September 2004 (Box 207, Folder 22)
      - Nolen, James Larry, granted 12 July 2004 (Box 208, Folder 1)
      - Norman, Margaret Ann, granted 26 July 2004 (Box 208, Folder 2)
      - Norwood, Shelton Ashburn, Jr., granted 18 February 2004 (Box 208, Folder 3)
      - Nottingham, Randy, granted 16 August 2004 (Box 208, Folder 3)
      - Nowlin, Charles M., granted 25 August 2004 (Box 208, Folder 3)
      - Nuccio, Robert Thomas, granted 28 May 2004 (Box 208, Folder 3)
      - Nugent, Keith A., granted 28 September 2004 (Box 208, Folder 3)
      - Nutter, Nathan Michael, granted 19 August 2004 (Box 208, Folder 3)
      - O'Connor, Donald M., granted 10 August 2004 (Box 208, Folder 4)
      - Oien, John Edward, granted 16 September 2004 (Box 208, Folder 4)
      - Olds, Leticia B., granted 23 February 2004 (Box 208, Folder 4)
      - Oliver, Lavinia Tereasa, granted 28 December 2004 (Box 208, Folder 4)
      - Oliver, Raymond Lee, Sr., granted 28 December 2004 (Box 208, Folder 4)
      - Oliver, Roger Dale, granted 7 July 2004 (Box 208, Folder 4)
      - O'Meara, William Michael, granted 28 December 2004 (Box 208, Folder 4)
      - Orender, William Delano, granted 18 August 2004 (Box 208, Folder 4)
      - Orne, Jessica S., granted 12 August 2004 (Box 208, Folder 5)
      - Owen, John David, granted 26 March 2004 (Box 208, Folder 5)
      - Owens, Melissa Lynn Stanley, granted 9 March 2004 (Box 208, Folder 5)
      - Owens-Pickett, Sheila Kay, granted 18 February 2004 (Box 208, Folder 5)
      - Painter, Ricky Lee, granted 12 February 2004 (Box 208, Folder 5)
      - Panizza, Richard E., granted 15 March 2004 (Box 208, Folder 5)
      - Parker, Avis Gwendolyn, granted 16 August 2004 (Box 208, Folder 6)
      - Parker, Isaac Lee, granted 7 July 2004 (Box 208, Folder 6)
      - Parris, Pamela Ann, granted 18 August 2004 (Box 208, Folder 6)
      - Patterson, Edward Byars, granted 12 July 2004 (Box 208, Folder 6)
      - Patterson, John Paul, granted 23 September 2004 (Box 208, Folder 6)
      - Patterson, Lionel Spencer, granted 25 February 2004 (Box 208, Folder 7)
      - Patterson, Raymond D., granted 24 August 2004 (Box 208, Folder 7)
      - Payne, Lynn Franklin, granted 2 August 2004 (Box 208, Folder 7)
      - Payne, William Robert, granted 2 August 2004 (Box 209, Folder 1)
      - Peake, Robert Stanley, granted 24 September 2004 (Box 209, Folder 1)
      - Pearce, Nancy M., granted 15 March 2004 (Box 209, Folder 1)
      - Pearce, Wayland Timothy, granted 21 June 2004 (Box 209, Folder 1)
      - Peck, Frank Morris, granted 19 July 2004 (Box 209, Folder 1)
      - Pekick, Eli, Jr., granted 2 July 2004 (Box 209, Folder 2)
      - Pennington, Leonard Franklin, granted 4 August 2004 (Box 209, Folder 2)
      - Perez, William Alberto, granted 13 April 2004 (Box 209, Folder 2)
      - Perkins, John Adam, Sr., granted 16 September 2004 (Box 209, Folder 2)
      - Perkinson, Deborah B., granted 26 July 2004 (Box 209, Folder 3)
      - Perry, Deborah Lock, granted 30 December 2004 (Box 209, Folder 3)
      - Perry, Edward Lee, granted 19 August 2004 (Box 209, Folder 3)
      - Petenbrink, Gordon W., granted 15 March 2004 (Box 209, Folder 3)
      - Peters, Kenneth Neil, granted 2 July 2004 (Box 209, Folder 4)
      - Peterson, James R., granted 4 August 2004 (Box 209, Folder 4)
      - Peterson, Paul David, granted 9 September 2004 (Box 209, Folder 4)
      - Petry, Rickey D., granted 18 February 2004 (Box 209, Folder 4)
      - Phillips, Charles Richard, granted 26 March 2004 (Box 209, Folder 4)
      - Phillips, Cletus, granted 22 March 2004 (Box 209, Folder 5)
      - Phillips, Iris Lynn, granted 12 February 2004 (Box 209, Folder 5)
      - Phillips, Keith Edward, Jr., granted 30 December 2004 (Box 209, Folder 5)
      - Phipps, Bradley W., granted 26 July 2004 (Box 209, Folder 5)
      - Pierce, Jerry Whit, granted 26 July 2004 (Box 209, Folder 5)
      - Pitrelli, John Frank, granted 16 August 2004 (Box 209, Folder 5)
      - Pitts, Charles Robert, granted 15 March 2004 (Box 209, Folder 5)
      - Plate, Karen Louise, granted 26 August 2004 (Box 210, Folder 1)
      - Poe, John Dunlap, granted 12 February 2004 (Box 210, Folder 1)
      - Poe, Patrick Kelly, granted 16 August 2004 (Box 210, Folder 1)
      - Poindexter, John E., Jr., granted 29 April 2004 (Box 210, Folder 1)
      - Pollard, Teresa W., granted 28 May 2004 (Box 210, Folder 1)
      - Porter, Toby Lee, granted 25 February 2004 (Box 210, Folder 2)
      - Porter, Vanessa Faye, granted 7 July 2004 (Box 210, Folder 2)
      - Poston, Billy Solomon, granted 19 August 2004 (Box 210, Folder 2)
      - Poston, Connie Lee, granted 13 April 2004 (Box 210, Folder 2)
      - Potter, Kenneth S., granted 11 May 2004 (Box 210, Folder 2)
      - Powell, Benjamin Hamilton, granted 21 January 2004 (Box 210, Folder 2)
      - Powell, Douglas Wayne, granted 11 May 2004 (Box 210, Folder 3)
      - Power, Dennis Wayne, Jr., granted 11 May 2004 (Box 210, Folder 3)
      - Price, Elizabeth Ann, granted 1 April 2004 (Box 210, Folder 3)
      - Price, Garnett Alan, granted 15 March 2004 (Box 210, Folder 3)
      - Price, Timothy Dale, granted 13 April 2004 (Box 210, Folder 3)
      - Pritchett, Joseph W., Jr., granted 15 March 2004 (Box 210, Folder 3)
      - Proctor, Wendy Brandford, granted 19 July 2004 (Box 210, Folder 4)
      - Propst, Steven Preston, granted 18 February 2004 (Box 210, Folder 4)
      - Pruitt, Horton L.C., granted 16 March 2004 (Box 210, Folder 4)
      - Pruitt, Michael Wayne, granted 12 August 2004 (Box 210, Folder 4)
      - Pryor, Rebecca Marie, granted 9 September 2004 (Box 210, Folder 4)
      - Puckett, Douglas Wayne, granted 11 May 2004 (Box 210, Folder 4)
      - Puckett, Otis Elbert, granted 26 July 2004 (Box 210, Folder 5)
      - Pugh, Debra Carol Stroupe, granted 12 July 2004 (Box 210, Folder 5)
      - Puryear, Lynette Trammell, granted 13 April 2004 (Box 210, Folder 5)
      - Quarles, Gene R., granted 25 August 2004 (Box 210, Folder 5)
      - Quigley, Michael John, granted 12 July 2004 (Box 210, Folder 5)
      - Raiford, Mary Rosenberger, granted 23 August 2004 (Box 211, Folder 1)
      - Randolph, Marvin A., granted 4 August 2004 (Box 211, Folder 1)
      - Ramos, Nathaniel Haskins, Jr., granted 9 March 2004 (Box 211, Folder 1)
      - Ramos, William Alexander, granted 1 June 2004 (Box 211, Folder 1)
      - Ratcliff, Carl Edward, granted 21 April 2004 (Box 211, Folder 1)
      - Ratcliff, Don Theodore, granted 26 March 2004 (Box 211, Folder 1)
      - Ray, Evelyn Denise, granted 26 March 2004 (Box 211, Folder 2)
      - Reaves, Robin Lynn, granted 12 July 2004 (Box 211, Folder 2)
      - Rector, Brenda Lynn, granted 23 August 2004 (Box 211, Folder 2)
      - Reed, Carlos Leon, granted 4 August 2004 (Box 211, Folder 2)
      - Reedy, Arvid Louis, granted 5 April 2004 (Box 211, Folder 2)
      - Reedy, Christopher Ray, granted 23 August 2004 (Box 211, Folder 2)
      - Reichard, Daniel H., Sr., granted 15 March 2004 (Box 211, Folder 2)
      - Reid, Alvinia Bianco, granted 10 August 2004 (Box 211, Folder 3)
      - Reid, Chris Adam, granted 16 September 2004 (Box 211, Folder 3)
      - Reidy, Darlene H., granted 24 August 2004 (Box 211, Folder 3)
      - Remele, Patricia A., granted 26 July 2004 (Box 211, Folder 3)
      - Reynolds, Gary Russell, II, granted 26 August 2004 (Box 211, Folder 3)
      - Rhodes, Samuel Randolph, granted 29 April 2004 (Box 211, Folder 3)
      - Ricks, Jerry W., granted 26 July 2004 (Box 211, Folder 3)
      - Riddle, Jerry Lee, granted 18 February 2004 (Box 211, Folder 4)
      - Ridgway, Charles Cleveland, granted 10 August 2004 (Box 211, Folder 4)
      - Rigney, Michael James, granted 12 July 2004 (Box 211, Folder 4)
      - Riner, Gary Wade, granted 21 May 2004 (Box 211, Folder 4)
      - Ritchie, Franklin Darrell, granted 26 July 2004 (Box 211, Folder 4)
      - Robbins, Jerry Mitchell, granted 6 July 2004 (Box 211, Folder 4)
      - Roberts, Darren C., granted 9 September 2004 (Box 211, Folder 5)
      - Roberts, Dwayne Leon, granted 26 July 2004 (Box 211, Folder 5)
      - Roberts, Janette S., granted 2 August 2004 (Box 211, Folder 5)
      - Robertson, Donald Gwynn, granted 14 January 2005 (Box 211, Folder 5)
      - Robertson, Robert Michael, granted 2 August 2004 (Box 211, Folder 5)
      - Robinson, Barbara, granted 12 August 2004 (Box 211, Folder 5)
      - Robinson, Freddie W., Jr., granted 9 March 2004 (Box 212, Folder 1)
      - Robinson, Karen Charmain, granted 18 August 2004 (Box 212, Folder 1)
      - Robinson, Patricia B., granted 28 December 2004 (Box 212, Folder 1)
      - Robinson, Roland Wayne, granted 6 July 2004 (Box 212, Folder 1)
      - Robson, Wyndom Ray, granted 2 July 2004 (Box 212, Folder 1)
      - Robuck, David Alan, granted 28 July 2004 (Box 212, Folder 1)
      - Rock, Clinton Alan, granted 24 September 2004 (Box 212, Folder 2)
      - Rodgers, Joseph Lewis, Jr., granted 23 September 2004 (Box 212, Folder 2)
      - Rogers, Christopher Norwin, granted 2 August 2004 (Box 212, Folder 2)
      - Rohrbaugh, Tony Wilson, granted 28 May 2004 (Box 212, Folder 2)
      - Roldan, Alberto, granted 26 July 2004 (Box 212, Folder 2)
      - Romero, Edenilson Giovanny, granted 17 March 2004 (Box 212, Folder 3)
      - Rose, Amber, granted 26 August 2004 (Box 212, Folder 3)
      - Rose, James Douglas, granted 24 September 2004 (Box 212, Folder 3)
      - Rose, Raymond Donald, Jr., granted 12 July 2004 (Box 212, Folder 3)
      - Ross, Edwina Marietta, granted 23 September 2004 (Box 212, Folder 3)
      - Ross, Susan M., granted 23 September 2004 (Box 212, Folder 4)
      - Rubis, Steven John, granted 12 February 2004 (Box 212, Folder 4)
      - Ruffin, Julius Earl, granted 30 March 2004 (Box 212, Folder 4)
      - Rupe, David Eugene, granted 19 August 2004 (Box 212, Folder 4)
      - Santmier, Phillip M., granted 9 March 2004 (Box 212, Folder 4)
      - Santuk, Edward F., Sr., granted 26 July 2004 (Box 212, Folder 4)
      - Saul, Gary Wayne, granted 21 May 2004 (Box 212, Folder 5)
      - Saunders, Clarence David, granted 26 August 2004 (Box 212, Folder 5)
      - Sayers, David Michael, granted 2 August 2004 (Box 212, Folder 5)
      - Scales, Alethia Ann, granted 30 December 2004 (Box 212, Folder 5)
      - Scarlett, Gary Wayne, granted 11 May 2004 (Box 212, Folder 5)
      - Schell, James R., granted 25 August 2004 (Box 212, Folder 5)
      - Schell, Sandra F., granted 25 August 2004 (Box 213, Folder 1)
      - Schipper, Diana Sarah, granted 26 July 2004 (Box 213, Folder 1)
      - Schirm, Timothy Lee, granted 28 December 2004 (Box 213, Folder 1)
      - Schlang, Elizabeth Ann, granted 19 August 2004 (Box 213, Folder 1)
      - Scholle, Esther Elaine, granted 16 September 2004 (Box 213, Folder 1)
      - Schuder, Mary Hodges, granted 13 April 2004 (Box 213, Folder 1)
      - Scott, Alfonza Bennett, granted 23 September 2004 (Box 213, Folder 1)
      - Scott, Anthony Drew, granted 29 April 2004 (Box 213, Folder 2)
      - Scott, Reginald E., granted 28 May 2004 (Box 213, Folder 2)
      - Seamster, Ira, III, granted 4 August 2004 (Box 213, Folder 2)
      - Seay, Andrew Wayne, granted 11 May 2004 (Box 213, Folder 2)
      - Sexton, Patrick Oliver, granted 16 September 2004 (Box 213, Folder 2)
      - Shackleford, Ronald Pride, granted 15 March 2004 (Box 213, Folder 3)
      - Sharitz, Michael Henry, granted 7 July 2004 (Box 213, Folder 3)
      - Sharpe, Stanley Edward, granted 16 September 2004 (Box 213, Folder 3)
      - Shears, Neville William, granted 2 July 2004 (Box 213, Folder 3)
      - Sheets, Marshall Nelson, granted 19 August 2004 (Box 213, Folder 3)
      - Shell, Cecil Edgar, granted 6 December 2004 (Box 213, Folder 3)
      - Sherrod, Tenuisha Novella, granted 11 May 2004 (Box 213, Folder 4)
      - Shifflett, Angela Marie, granted 23 February 2004 (Box 213, Folder 4)
      - Shifflett, Archie Lee, granted 26 August 2004 (Box 213, Folder 4)
      - Shifflett, Bruce Rodney, granted 18 February 2004 (Box 213, Folder 4)
      - Shifflett, Fred Gilbert, granted 14 January 2005 (Box 213, Folder 4)
      - Shifflett, Susan Maureen, granted 16 January 2004 (Box 213, Folder 4)
      - Shiflett, Robby Lee, granted 7 May 2004 (Box 213, Folder 5)
      - Shipp, Michael Bertis, granted 9 September 2004 (Box 213, Folder 5)
      - Shomaker, Edwin Baker, granted 12 August 2004 (Box 213, Folder 5)
      - Short, William Richard, Jr., granted 4 August 2004 (Box 213, Folder 5)
      - Showers, Bernice Chaney Gunn, granted 4 August 2004 (Box 213, Folder 5)
      - Simmons, David, Jr., granted 9 March 2004 (Box 213, Folder 5)
      - Simmons, Kelly Jean, granted 30 December 2004 (Box 214, Folder 1)
      - Simmons, Lester Delice, granted 2 August 2004 (Box 214, Folder 1)
      - Simpkins, Janice Edna, granted 2 August 2004 (Box 214, Folder 1)
      - Simpson, Gregory Edward, granted 6 December 2004 (Box 214, Folder 1)
      - Simpson, Howard Andrew, granted 16 March 2004 (Box 214, Folder 2)
      - Sims, Dewey William, granted 29 December 2004 (Box 214, Folder 2)
      - Sink, Jimmie Raymond, granted 16 March 2004 (Box 214, Folder 2)
      - Sirbaugh, Judy Ann, granted 23 August 2004 (Box 214, Folder 2)
      - Sisk, Harry C., Sr., granted 29 September 2004 (Box 214, Folder 2)
      - Sisk, Ronnie Jerrold, granted 12 February 2004 (Box 214, Folder 3)
      - Skeens, Jerry Dennis, granted 20 January 2004 (Box 214, Folder 3)
      - Skeens, Terry Steven, granted 29 September 2004 (Box 214, Folder 3)
      - Sluss, Jeffrey N., granted 6 December 2004 (Box 214, Folder 3)
      - Small, Carlton Wayne, granted 2 July 2004 (Box 214, Folder 3)
      - Smalley, David G., granted 12 August 2004 (Box 214, Folder 3)
      - Smelser, Roger O'Dell, granted 21 May 2004 (Box 214, Folder 4)
      - Smith, Alvin Wayne, granted 9 March 2004 (Box 214, Folder 4)
      - Smith, Claudette Irene, granted 23 November 2004 (Box 214, Folder 4)
      - Smith, David Eugene, granted 19 August 2004 (Box 214, Folder 4)
      - Smith, Harold R., granted 30 December 2004 (Box 214, Folder 4)
      - Smith, Jimmy Leon, granted 18 August 2004 (Box 214, Folder 4)
      - Smith, Kelly Robert, granted 30 March 2004 (Box 214, Folder 4)
      - Smith, Patricia, granted 30 December 2004 (Box 214, Folder 5)
      - Smith, Paul Douglas, granted 18 February 2004 (Box 214, Folder 5)
      - Smukal, Fawn Michelle Lewis, granted 13 April 2004 (Box 214, Folder 5)
      - Snapp, David Scott, granted 9 September 2004 (Box 214, Folder 5)
      - Snyder, Keith Gustave, granted 21 May 2004 (Box 214, Folder 5)
      - Snyder, Mary Jane, granted 26 August 2004 (Box 214, Folder 5)
      - Spangler, Joe Aubrey, granted 12 August 2004 (Box 214, Folder 5)
      - Sparks, Paul Eugene, Jr., granted 23 September 2004 (Box 215, Folder 1)
      - Spaulding, Kenneth Eugene, granted 16 August 2004 (Box 215, Folder 1)
      - Speas, Daniel Robert, granted 1 July 2004 (Box 215, Folder 1)
      - Spence, Jannet Sutton, granted 26 July 2004 (Box 215, Folder 1)
      - Spencer, Johnnie, Jr., granted 5 March 2004 (Box 215, Folder 1)
      - Spiggle, Jeffrey Kim, granted 26 April 2004 (Box 215, Folder 1)
      - Spradlin, India Farrar, granted 2 August 2004 (Box 215, Folder 2)
      - Sprott, Joseph Briggs, granted 21 May 2004 (Box 215, Folder 2)
      - Sprouse, Bonnie, granted 26 July 2004 (Box 215, Folder 2)
      - Sprouse, Rita Kite, granted 26 July 2004 (Box 215, Folder 2)
      - Spurlock, Eddie Gene, granted 19 August 2004 (Box 215, Folder 2)
      - Stacy, Danny Ray, granted 21 May 2004 (Box 215, Folder 3)
      - Stadlin, Kenneth Paul, granted 15 March 2004 (Box 215, Folder 3)
      - Stakes, Donald Ray, Sr., granted 2 December 2004 (Box 215, Folder 3)
      - Stallard, Robert Lee, granted 26 July 2004 (Box 215, Folder 3)
      - Stallings, James Harold, Jr., granted 30 December 2004 (Box 215, Folder 3)
      - Stanley, Walter J., Jr., granted 28 December 2004 (Box 215, Folder 3)
      - Starinieri, Timothy Chapman, granted 11 May 2004 (Box 215, Folder 4)
      - St. Clair, Crockett Andrew, granted 7 July 2004 (Box 215, Folder 4)
      - Staton, Liger William, granted 26 July 2004 (Box 215, Folder 4)
      - Stearns, Rosalind Estes, granted 16 August 2004 (Box 215, Folder 4)
      - Stefano, Anthony John, granted 21 May 2004 (Box 215, Folder 4)
      - Stephens, Carolyn Kay, granted 16 September 2004 (Box 215, Folder 5)
      - Stephens, William Curtis, Jr., granted 18 August 2004 (Box 215, Folder 5)
      - Stepp, Kenneth Richard, granted 26 July 2004 (Box 215, Folder 5)
      - Steppe, George Jeffrey, granted 10 August 2004 (Box 215, Folder 5)
      - Stevens, John Thomas, granted 16 September 2004 (Box 215, Folder 5)
      - Stevens, Robert L., granted 26 July 2004 (Box 215, Folder 5)
      - Stewart, Michael Lee, granted 11 May 2004 (Box 216, Folder 1)
      - Stewart, Michael Lee, granted 11 May 2004 (Box 216, Folder 1)
      - Stewart, Vanessa M., granted 26 July 2004 (Box 216, Folder 1)
      - Stiff, Jeffrey Byron, granted 18 February 2004 (Box 216, Folder 1)
      - Stohlman, Glenn P., granted 28 September 2004 (Box 216, Folder 1)
      - Stone, Michael Russell, granted 12 August 2004 (Box 216, Folder 1)
      - Stonebreaker, Stephen Everett, granted 26 August 2004 (Box 216, Folder 2)
      - Story, Deborah Lynn, granted 10 February 2004 (Box 216, Folder 2)
      - Stovall, Suzette Virginia, granted 10 August 2004 (Box 216, Folder 2)
      - Stratton, William Ernest, granted 26 July 2004 (Box 216, Folder 2)
      - Stroupe, Clenton E., granted 13 April 2004 (Box 216, Folder 2)
      - Stroupe, Nancy C., granted 13 April 2004 (Box 216, Folder 2)
      - Sturgell, Darrell James, granted 25 February 2004 (Box 216, Folder 2)
      - Suttle, Robert Vinton, III, granted 1 July 2004 (Box 216, Folder 3)
      - Swanson, Lawrence Jerome, granted 4 June 2004 (Box 216, Folder 3)
      - Swieder, Robert Eugene, granted 26 July 2004 (Box 216, Folder 3)
      - Sykes, James B., Jr., granted 29 April 2004 (Box 216, Folder 3)
      - Sykes, William Alexander, granted 23 September 2004 (Box 216, Folder 3)
      - Tait, James Timothy, granted 10 August 2004 (Box 216, Folder 3)
      - Tallant, Allen Wade, granted 11 May 2004 (Box 216, Folder 4)
      - Tate, Tracy Lynette, granted 7 July 2004 (Box 216, Folder 4)
      - Taylor, Burton Ashby, Sr., granted 30 December 2004 (Box 216, Folder 4)
      - Taylor, Larry Richard, granted 9 March 2004 (Box 216, Folder 4)
      - Taylor, Lynn Oscar, II, granted 26 August 2004 (Box 216, Folder 4)
      - Taylor, Richard Walter, granted 30 August 2004 (Box 216, Folder 4)
      - Terry, Barbara Ann, granted 19 August 2004 (Box 216, Folder 4)
      - Thacker, Jeffrey Myles, granted 26 July 2004 (Box 216, Folder 5)
      - Thatcher, Jack Brian, granted 16 August 2004 (Box 216, Folder 5)
      - Thomas, Roderick Sterling, granted 12 August 2004 (Box 216, Folder 5)
      - Thomas, Stanley, granted 1 July 2004 (Box 216, Folder 5)
      - Thompson, Danny Eugene, Jr., granted 9 March 2004 (Box 216, Folder 5)
      - Thompson, Juanita Anderson, granted 13 April 2004 (Box 216, Folder 5)
      - Thompson, Philip Chester, granted 28 September 2004 (Box 216, Folder 5)
      - Thompson, Roxann Mae Woolwine, granted 23 August 2004 (Box 217, Folder 1)
      - Thompson, Vernard Lee Randolf, granted 9 September 2004 (Box 217, Folder 1)
      - Thorne, Russell Clinton, Jr., granted 1 July 2004 (Box 217, Folder 1)
      - Thorogood, Jo Ann, granted 18 August 2004 (Box 217, Folder 1)
      - Thornton, Sheron Denise, granted 26 July 2004 (Box 217, Folder 1)
      - Thornton, Sylvia Jean, granted 21 May 2004 (Box 217, Folder 1)
      - Thumel, Martha Gabel, granted 21 April 2004 (Box 217, Folder 2)
      - Tignor, Norman Lane, Jr., granted 15 March 2004 (Box 217, Folder 2)
      - Tilson, Mark A., granted 28 May 2004 (Box 217, Folder 2)
      - Timmons, Angela Priscilla, granted 24 September 2004 (Box 217, Folder 2)
      - Tinsley, Jeffrey Dean, granted 9 March 2004 (Box 217, Folder 2)
      - Tomardy, Deborah A., granted 18 August 2004 (Box 217, Folder 2)
      - Tomblin, Edgar Monroe, granted 2 December 2004 (Box 217, Folder 3)
      - Torrence, Frank Clifton, granted 12 August 2004 (Box 217, Folder 3)
      - Trainham, Wayne Ray, granted 29 September 2004 (Box 217, Folder 3)
      - Trammell, Robert Wayne, granted 2 December 2004 (Box 217, Folder 3)
      - Trawitzki, Paul Francis, granted 29 April 2004 (Box 217, Folder 3)
      - Trent, Herbert A., granted 7 July 2004 (Box 217, Folder 3)
      - Trent, Ronnie Lee, granted 7 July 2004 (Box 217, Folder 4)
      - Tretola, Andrew, granted 23 November 2004 (Box 217, Folder 4)
      - Tribble, George Burnette, granted 29 September 2004 (Box 217, Folder 4)
      - Tribby, Kevin L, granted 7 May 2004 (Box 217, Folder 4)
      - Trimble, Claude Wilbur, Jr., granted 13 April 2004 (Box 217, Folder 4)
      - Truslow, Donald Ray, granted 2 July 2004 (Box 217, Folder 4)
      - Trusty, Monica Charlene, granted 10 August 2004 (Box 217, Folder 5)
      - Tsiamis, Arthur William, granted 16 August 2004 (Box 217, Folder 5)
      - Tunstall, Yvonne Harris, granted 12 February 2004 (Box 217, Folder 5)
      - Tylee, Venus Gayle, granted 6 December 2004 (Box 217, Folder 5)
      - VanDeRiet, Earl Woodrow, Jr., granted 21 April 2004 (Box 217, Folder 5)
      - VanValkenburg, Samuel Lief, granted 13 April 2004 (Box 217, Folder 5)
      - Vance, John Gary, granted 25 August 2004 (Box 217, Folder 5)
      - Vaughan, Charles Ellis, granted 12 July 2004 (Box 218, Folder 1)
      - Vaughan, Frances C., granted 23 November 2004 (Box 218, Folder 1)
      - Vaughter, Shanel C., granted 7 July 2004 (Box 218, Folder 1)
      - Vega, Anthony, granted 13 April 2004 (Box 218, Folder 1)
      - Vennie, Joyce Ann Lewis, granted 29 September 2004 (Box 218, Folder 1)
      - Vernon, Barbara Taylor, granted 29 September 2004 (Box 218, Folder 1)
      - Via, Christopher Craig, granted 21 May 2004 (Box 218, Folder 2)
      - Via, Dionne M., granted 4 June 2004 (Box 218, Folder 2)
      - Vick, Jack A., granted 26 August 2004 (Box 218, Folder 2)
      - Vines, John Lyle, Jr., granted 4 June 2004 (Box 218, Folder 2)
      - Viola, Michael Christopher, granted 30 August 2004 (Box 218, Folder 2)
      - Vitatoe, Hubert, Jr., granted 26 July 2004 (Box 218, Folder 3)
      - Wade, Donald Lee, Sr., granted 19 August 2004 (Box 218, Folder 3)
      - Wade-Booker, Nancy C., granted 18 February 2004 (Box 218, Folder 3)
      - Wagner, Karin Renee, granted 19 August 2004 (Box 218, Folder 3)
      - Waite, William A., granted 15 March 2004 (Box 218, Folder 4)
      - Wales, Samuel S., III, granted 4 August 2004 (Box 218, Folder 4)
      - Walker, Carols Edward, granted 9 March 2004 (Box 218, Folder 4)
      - Walker, Donald Wayne, granted 21 April 2004 (Box 218, Folder 4)
      - Walker, Gloria R., granted 21 April 2004 (Box 218, Folder 4)
      - Waller, Robert Lee, granted 25 August 2004 (Box 218, Folder 4)
      - Walsh, Scott Christopher, granted 12 August 2004 (Box 218, Folder 5)
      - Walters, Rita E., granted 2 August 2004 (Box 218, Folder 5)
      - Walton, Agnes, granted 29 September 2004 (Box 218, Folder 5)